Mic check, one. [Laughter]
I can't wait for you guys to try this.
For the entire month of July at Tuscan Cove,
you're gonna get the Antonio Loves Wings special.
I'm with Chef Romo.
We're making a chimichurri.
Chef, tell me a little bit about this.
We wanted to collaborate on a little hot for the summer
because it's hot.
We got a little honey, a little lemon juice,
A little dried chili, a little habanero,
jalapenos, some garlic,
a little bit of cilantro to finish it off.
What are we gonna taste with it?
Wings, baby, look at these wings.
Come over here and take a look at that.
Real good, man.
That's so good.
Just line them up.
With that sauce right here.
Let's hit it with a little bit more color.
Why not?
We got Antonio's Latin wings right there, baby.
Antonio loves wings.
Ooh, that's a hot wing.
Salud.
That's sweet.
That's my favorite right there.
I can't wait for you guys to try this.
This is amazing.
Come see us at Tuscan Cove.
We're gonna run these [unclear].
Just ask for Antonio's wings.